Guide to the Apple Computer, Inc. Records M1007
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Marketing, Advertising & Sales, Series 7
  - Macintosh Sales Aids, Subseries 7.18
    - Upgrades & updates chart, 1991 Jan.; 3 posters (Box Nb5)
    - Upgrades & updates chart, 1991 Mar.; 1 poster (Box Nb5)
    - Macintosh compatibility chart, 1992 Jan.; 2 posters (Box Nb5)
    - Macintosh compatibility chart, 1993 Mar.; 2 posters (Box Nb5)
    - Apple compatibility chart, 1994 May; 1 poster (Box Nb5)
    - HyperTalk highlights, 1988; 1 poster (Box Nb5)
  - General Sales Training Materials, Subseries 7.19
    - Logo Information, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Apple Means Business Merchandising Plan Training Manual, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Apple Macintosh Certification Training Leader's Guide, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
    - Apple Account Penetration Strategies Training, undated (Box 27, Folder 7-8)
    - Apple Means Business Merchandising Plan Training Manual, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Apple Means Business Merchandising Plan Training Manual, undated (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - "Intelligent Choices" Merchandising Plan Training Materials, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      Audiocassette And Slides
    - "Intelligent Choices" Merchandising Plan Training Materials, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - "Intelligent Choices" Merchandising Plan Training Materials, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - "Intelligent Choices" Merchandising Plan Training Materials, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - "Intelligent Choices" Merchandising Plan Training Materials Catalog, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Sales Meeting [Hawaii], 1981 (Box 28, Folder 8-11)
      Slides in Saperate Folder
    - Apple Expo. Tools for Today, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - List of Educational Software Developed for Apple, 1982, Jan. (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Product Marketing Staff Binder, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      1981 Dec. - 1982 Apr.
      Scott Love
    - Here's H.O.W. to Sell 40 Apples in 1 Day, 1982 ? (Box 29, Folder 4)
      Hands on Workshop
    - National Account Pgm Executive Slide Presentation, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      Diskette, Slides
    - ProFile Sales Kit, 1982 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Selling Personal Computers: Apple's Guide for the Department Store, 1982 ? (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Announcement for 256k Upgrade Kits for Apple III's, 1982, June (Box 29, Folder 16)
      U.K.
    - Field Sales Information, 1982 Jan.- Nov. (Box 29, Folder 8-15)
    - Misc. Info on Software Products, 1982-1997 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Info on Hard Ware and Peripherals, 1982-1997 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - National Account Program, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Value Added Reseller Program Manual, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Logo Sales Kit, 1983, July (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Apple Horizons: Small Business and Professional Practice Sales Seminar, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Horizons, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - The Sales Lists, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Apple University In pursuit of Excellence, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - In pursuit of Excellence, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Memo re: Mac and Lisa 2 for National Account Employee Purchase, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Apple Education Sales Manual, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 3-4)
      Two Folders
    - National Account Program Communications / Reference Guide, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Impressions: A Modular Presentation and Seminar Guide, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 6-7)
    - 1984 Regional Sales Conference (Box 32, Folder 1-2)
    - User Education Archives [sic.] Inventory Sorted by Part, Product Or Title, 1985, Aug. (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Misc. Sales and Ad Images, 1985? (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Macintosh Office Sales Aids, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Apple Computer and Northern Telecom Capabilities Presentation, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Apple Vertical Market Business [Software] Directory, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - System Guides for Mac and Apple, 1987? (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Program of Events Worldwide Sales Conference, Boca Raton FL, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Education Installation Purchase Program Procedures, 1987, June (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Service Programs Manual, 1988, Dec. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Information on Services and Support, 1988-1997 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Visuals for Power to Be Your Best" Presentation, 1988 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Education Sales Manual, 1988, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - The Information Exchange: Update, 1988, Oct. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Apple Distribution: A View to the Future... The Basics: Customer Satisfaction, Quality, Service, 1989, Apr. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - The Information Exchange: Marketing Guidebook, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Disketts
    - The Information Exchange: Marketing Guidebook, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - New Products Brochures, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - The Very Informative Guide to Selling Apple, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      Version 2.0
    - A Guide to Successful Distribution in Australia, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - New Product Training, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - New Product Information, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Competitive Selling Guide, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Masters of Media Sales Aid, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Newton Healthcare Solutions Guide, 1996 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Apple Competitive Guide, 1996-1997 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Apple sales discipline. Note: associated transparencies in Series 7, FB 35, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Apple USA FY '91 sales conference materials, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 1 - 10 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 11 - 20 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 21 - 30 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 31 - 40 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 41 - 50 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Apple sales discipline [transparency], 1985: subject no. 51 - 60 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Business Ventures (Third Party Ventures and Products), Series 8
  This series includes proposals and agreements between Apple and other groups to develop, produce or manufacture products compatible with or specifically for Apple products.
  - Third Party Information, Subseries 8.1
    - Apple Developer Express (product descriptions & brochures), 1987 Winter (Box 1, Folder 1 -4)
      four folders
    - Apple Developer Express (product descriptions & brochures), 1987 Summer (Box 1, Folder 5 -7)
    - Aquisition of Network Innovations Corp., 1988, Mar. (Box 2, Folder 4)
      bound volume
      Network Innovations Corp.
    - User Guide & Greatest Hits software collection, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      Ziff Net
    - IntroNews: the third party source. Vol. 3, No. 1, 1992, Jan. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Apple Developer Express (product descriptions & brochures), 1987 Fall (Box 2, Folder 1 -3)
    - Intelligent oscilloscope system proposal, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      KRJ Systems, Inc.
    - Universal Micro catalog, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Valiant IMC
    - user's manual, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Dynamac machine itself is also part of M1007 collection
      Dynamac Computer Products, Inc.
    - Syllabus, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - RedRyder 6.2 manual, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      FreeSoft Company
    - policy re: third party products at Apple Library & Apple Employee store, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bitguard letter, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
      Renola, Ed
    - Apple & Microsoft outline plans for future joint technologies, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 10)
      Microsoft
    - Apple & Novell: working together on network solutions, 1994? (Box 3, Folder 11)
      Novell
    - Macintosh business conference & exposition, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - confirmation letter re: registration of file types & application signatures, 1990, Nov. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - The Recognizer Project, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 14)
      Carl Nelson & Associates
    - new products & features, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Miko Kiosks, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
      King Products
    - KaleidaScript X developer catalog, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 17)
      Kaleida Labs
    - CEO 1401 Intelligent Laboratory Interface for Apple II, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
      Cambridge Electronic Design Ltd.
    - Apple II & Apple IIe hardware compatibility guides, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - products for the Apple II family, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - new third party products for Apple hardware & software, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Apple CD SC third party products, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - list of products that support one or more Apple II peripherals, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    - Third Party information (System 7), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Apple III software resource guide, 1983, Mar. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Hayden Macintosh Library, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Hayden Book Company
    - The Keyboard Company [Cork, Ireland], 1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      The Keyboard Company
    - Mactivity '96, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Milliken: continuing medical education, 1979? (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - NeXT, 1993-1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      NeXT
    - AppleCD SC third party products, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Softape, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - The NeXTketeer [newsletter], undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - information on NeXT acquisition, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Business & Professional Software, Inc. Apple color plotter announcement, undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Highton virtual reality photography brochure, undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Press releases & clippings, Subseries 9
  This series includes information produced specifically to be released to the press and/or the public regarding Apple Computer, Inc. and its products, as well as press clippings about Apple Computer and its competitors.
  - Press Kits & Media Guidelines, Subseries 9.1
    - The World of Apple, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Inquiries from the Press, Media Guidelines., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Apple Information Press Kit, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Press Background Information, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Macintosh Office Press Kit, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - New Products Press Kit, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Apple Networking And Communications Product Introduction Press Kit, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Happy Birthday Macintosh Press Kit, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - System 7 Press Information, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Press Releases, Subseries 9.2
    - Press Releases, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Press Releases, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      includes list of releases
    - Press Releases, 1986-1991 (Box 2, Folder 1-6)
    - Index to Press Releases (1995-1998) (Box 3, Folder 10)
      frpm Apple Website
    - Press Releases, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 1-9)
    - Press Releases, 1995, Jan. - 1996, Sept. (Box 4, Folder 1-7)
  - Clippings (general), Subseries 9.3
    - Loose Clippings, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Loose Clippings, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Byte Magaxine Article Reprint: System Description - The Apple II, 1977, May (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Loose Clippings, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Inc. Premiere Issue., 1979, Apr. (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Softalk, 1981, Mar. (Box 5, Folder 14)
      women in microcomputing issue
    - Press Releases, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
    - The Journal of Courseware Review (Apple II), 1981? (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Clippings, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Clippings, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 11-13)
    - The Apple Index, 1983, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Seybold Report on Professional Computing Vol. 1 No. 1, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Apple Orchard Vol. 5 No. 2, 1984, Feb. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - MacWorld Vol. 1 No. 1, 1984, Feb. (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Computer Update, 1984, Mar. - Apr. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Softalk, 1984, July (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Info World Vol. 6 Issue 19, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      Laptops
    - The Seybold Report on Professional Computing, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Newsweek., 1984, Nov./Dec. (Box 6, Folder 12)
      all ads are Apple
    - Clippings, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Clippings, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
    - Management Technology Vol. 2 No. 9, 1985, Jan. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Compate! Vol 2. No1, Issue 3, 1986, Spring/ Summer (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - L'Ordinatear Individuel No. 69, 1985, Apr. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Medias No. 117 Du4 Au 11, 1985, Oct. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Personal Computer Forum Vol. 2 Release 1.0, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - inCider. Vol. 4 No. 10, 1986, Oct. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Family Computing Vol. 4 No. 10, 1986, Oct. (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - International Press Interviews with Sculley, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Clippings Re: John Sculley Book "Odyssey", 1987 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Information Week Issue 106, 1987, Mar. 2 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Clippings, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5-6)
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11-12)
    - Wharton Alumni Magazine, 1987, Fall. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hyper Age Premiere Issue, 1988 Feb. - Mar. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Public Relations Clippings #388, 1988 July (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Happy Birthday Macintosh, Special 10yr. Anniversary Information, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Clippings, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 5-10)
    - Clippings, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 1-5)
    - San Francisco Chronicle article re: use of Macintosh computers to produce newspaper after earthquake, 1989 Oct. 18 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - MAXpowr card: big bang for buck / by Henry Norr. -- MacWeek, Vol. 11, no. 39, 1997 Oct. 13 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Lisa announcement press book, France. Note: presented to M. Markkula, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Clippings (Burrelle's, etc.), Subseries 9.4
    - Clippings, 1983- 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6-8)
    - Clippings, 1985 Oct. - 1986 Jan. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Clippings, 1984 Mar. - 1985 Sept. (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1985 Sept. (Box 10, Folder 4-6)
    - Clippings, 1985 Oct. - 1986 Jan. (Box 11, Folder 1-2)
    - Clippings, 1986 Jan. - Apr. (Box 11, Folder 3-5)
    - Clippings, 1986 May - June (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1986 June - Oct. (Box 12, Folder 4-5)
    - Clippings, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1987 Sept.-Oct. (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - Apple / DEC Ammounce Joint Development, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1988 June- Aug. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1988 Jan. - Mar. (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
    - Clippings, 1988 Aug. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1988 Aug. - Sept. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1988 Sept. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1988 Oct. (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - Clippings, 1988 Oct. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1988 Oct. -Nov. (Box 16, Folder 2-5)
    - Clippings, 1988 Dec. (Box 17, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1989 Jan. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1989 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
    - Clippings, 1989 Jan. (Box 18, Folder 3-5)
    - Clippings, 1989 Mar. (Box 19, Folder 1-3)
    - Clippings, 1989 Apr. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1989 Apr. (Box 20, Folder 1-2)
    - Clippings, 1989 May (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
    - Clippings, 1989 May (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Clippings, 1989 June. 1-10 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1989 June. 12-21 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1989 June 21 - July 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1989 July (Box 22, Folder 2-4)
    - Clippings, 1989 July 31-Aug. 7 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1989 Aug. 8-21 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1989 Aug. 21-30 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1989 Aug. 31 - Sept. 19 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1989 Sept. 20-Nov.30 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1989 Dec. 1-13 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1989 Dec. 14-22 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1989 Dec. 24-31; 1990 Jan. (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1990 Jan. 1-8 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1990 Jan. 9-16 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Clippings, 1990 Jan. 17-23 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1990 Jan. 24-30 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Clippings (Sculley clipbooks), Subseries 9.5
    - Clippings, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Clippings, 1993 Aug. 2,3,4 Sept. 28 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Clippings (Macintosh), Subseries 9.6
    - Macintosh Vol.1, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Macintosh Vol.2, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Macintosh Vol.3, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Macintosh Vol.4, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous, Subseries 9.7
    - Author Incentive Program Database Printout, 1983? (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Apple Farm. Book for People Who Loves [sic.] Apple, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      Japanese Language
    - Press Conferences Europe: Lle, Lisa, 1983 Jan. - Feb. (Box 27, Folder 7)
      Lie, Lisa
    - www.apple.com, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Manuals & Guides
  - anniversary publications, 1987, 1997 (Box 10)
  - Apple IIgs Reference Manuals (Box 6)
  - AppleLink manuals (Box 7)
  - Apple manuals, misc. (Box 15)
  - Apple Media Kit (with demonstration Compact Disc) (Box 13)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit [not numbered] - includes VHS tape, 1994 (Box 82)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit [not numbered] - includes VHS tape and data CDs, 1995 (Box 82)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit [not numbered] - includes VHS tape and data CD, 1994 (Box 83)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit [not numbered] - includes data CDs and 3.5" floppy discs (Box 92)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit No. 1 and 2 - includes VHS tapes, 1996 (Box 82)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit No. 2 - includes VHS tape, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit No. 2 - includes VHS tape, 1995 (Box 83)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit No. 3 - inlcudes enhanced CD, 1995 (Box 81)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit: Macintosh Programmers Workshop, 1992 (Box 89)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit: Macintosh Programmers Workshop Assembler Reference, 1993 (Box 89)
  - Apple Self-paced Orientation Tool Kit - includes data CD and VHS tape, 1994 (Box 84)
  - AppleShare manuals (Box 6)
  - Apple Multimedia Kit No. 1 - includes data CDs, 1994 (Box 83)
  - Apple software, misc. (Box 15)
  - AppleTalk for programmers: self-paced training - includes CD, 1992 (Box 84)
  - Appleworks Journal, Exclusive Reference, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
  - CD-ROM Authoring Manual (Box 10)
  - CD-ROM manuals (Box 7)
  - Design 96 student project w/CD-ROM, VHS cassette (Box 10)
  - developer guides - SADE, MPW, "The Information Binder," ProDosTech reference manual (Box 9)
  - Developer University Mini Course: Programming with MPW, 1992 (Box 87)
  - Developer University Mini Course: QuickTime Programming Tutotial - includes CD-ROMs, 1992 (Box 87)
  - educational material - Resource Guides, Apple Access, etc. (Box 9)
  - EtherTalk manuals (Box 6)
  - general product reference guides, 1981-1990 (Box 2)
  - hardware marketing brochures (Box 10)
  - hardware manuals - cables, scanners, cards, drives, monitors, printers, etc. (Box 7)
  - HyperCard manuals (Box 6)
  - HyperTalk manuals (Box 6)
  - Inside Macintosh Service Modules, Quicktime (Box 3)
  - Inside Macintosh v.1-6 (includes different editions) (Box 3)
  - Inside Macintosh X-Ref (Box 3)
  - Lisa manuals, software, brochures (Box 8)
  - Macintosh LC manuals (Box 4)
  - Macintosh 8500 Specifications (Box 4)
  - Macintosh manuals - Getting Started - Classic II, Color Classic, Quadra 610, 840, 950 (Box 4)
  - Mac OS Essentials Kit - containsa data CD, 1994 (Box 84)
  - Macintosh Product Training Kit (includes audio cassette & VHS videocassette) (Box 13)
  - Macintosh Product Registry, 1994-1996 (Box 2)
  - Macintosh Programming Fundatmentals - includes CD-ROM, 1991 (Box 87)
  - Macintosh Reference, 1990-1991 (Box 4)
  - Macintosh System 7.5 Upgrade Guide (Box 4)
  - Macintosh System Software User's Guide (Box 4)
  - Macintosh User's Guides - Classic, Performa, Powerbook, Powerbook 145, Powerbook 210 & 230 (Box 4)
  - Macintosh User's Manuals - Performa 5400, 6400; Powerbook 2400c, 3400; PowerMac 9500, 8500, 8600, 9600, 5200/5300, 4400, 5260, 5200/75, 6500, 7300, 5500, 7600 (Box 4)
  - Macintosh Utilities User's Guides (Box 6)
  - manual drafts & revisions (Box 7)
  - Media Kits - Ziff Forum et al., 1994-1995 (Box 80)
  - Mice, third party, assorted - in original packaging (Box 135)
  - Microsoft manuals & software - Powerpoint, Excel, Works, etc. (Box 14)
  - misc. third party software (Box 15)
  - misc. manuals (Box 1)
  - misc. manuals & guides - Apple II, IIc, IIe, AppleWorks (Box 5)
  - misc. manuals - MultiFinder, REedit, Photoflash, Dylan, etc. (Box 7)
  - misc. marketing publications- catalogs, newsletters, press releases, etc. Mostly by Apple., 1980-1997 (Box 11)
  - misc. Quick Reference guides & warranty information (Box 4)
  - misc. third party software & manuals - Claris, Visicorp, Symantec (Box 13)
  - Owner's Manuals- Macintosh II, IIx, IIcx, Plus SE, SE/30 (Box 2)
  - PC Compatibility manuals (Box 7)
  - Photoflash Media Kit, 1994 (Box 88)
  - Personal Training Kits, various programs - include audio cassettes and 3.5" floppy discs, 1990-1992 (Box 84)
  - Personal Training Kits, various programs - include audio cassettes and 3.5" floppy discs, 1990-1992 (Box 86)
  - Personal Training Kits, various programs - include audio cassettes and 3.5" floppy discs, circa 1992 (Box 85)
  - Powertalk Templates, 1993 (Box 87)
  - Quicktime VR Authoring Tools (Box 10)
  - sales & marketing slides (Box 11)
  - Server manuals (Box 7)
  - software - HyperCard; System Software UG604; Applesoft Programmmer's Kit; AppleWorks, Lisa Office system, Quicktime Starter Kit, etc. (Box 12)
  - Software Training Kits, assorted - include software, audio and video media (Box 133)
  - Software Training Kits, assorted - include software, audio and video media (Box 134)
  - Software Training Kits, assorted - include software, audio and video media (Box 135)
  - software marketing brochures (Box 10)
  - "Take It Or Leave It" Technical Resources, 1989 (Box 10)
  - Teaching, Learning & Technology Planning Guide (Box 10)
  - Technical Introduction to the Mac Family (Box 4)
  - Intermediate PageMaker 5.0, Vol. 2; 1 floppy diskette, 1 audio cassette, 2 training guides, 1993 (Oversize-box 160)
  - Intermediate PageMaker 5.0, Vol. 3; 1 floppy diskette, 1 audio cassette, 3 training guides, 1992 (Oversize-box 160)
  - Intermediate Freehand: Aldus Freehand 3.1, Vol. 2; 1 floppy diskette, 1 audio cassette, 2 training guides (Oversize-box 160)
  - Developer University Mini Course Quick Time Programming Tutorial; 1 manual, 1992 (Oversize-box 160)
  - Quick Reference Booklet: Macintosh IIci Computer Training; 2 floppy diskettes, 1 booklet, 1989 (Oversize-box 161)
  - Quick Reference Booklet: Macintosh IIcx Computer Training; 1 floppy diskette, 1 audio cassette, 1 booklet, 1989 (Oversize-box 161)
  - Quick Reference Booklet: Apple IIGS and System Software 5.0; 1 floppy diskette, 1 video cassette, 1 booklet, 1989 (Oversize-box 161)
  - Quick Reference Booklet: Macintosh Portable Training, 1 floppy diskette, 1 audio cassette, 1 video cassette, 1 booklet, 1989 (Oversize-box 161)
  - Developer University Self-Paced Training: Macintosh User-Centered Design, 1 floppy diskette, 1 video cassette, 1 work book (Oversize-box 161)
  - The Author's Solution: For Interactive Electronic Books; 1 CD-ROM, 5 guide books (2 copies), 1993 (Box 162)
  - Mac OS Essentials Kit: System Strategy and Solutions Demos; 1 CD-ROM, various material guides, 1994 (Box 162)
  - Self-Paced Orientation Tool Kit: Apple Orientation Training Just Got Easier; 1 CD-ROM, 1 video cassette, 2 booklets, 1 Apple campatibility chart (2 copies), 1994 (Box 162)
  - Macintosh Fundamentals Interactive Learning Course; 3 laserdiscs, 1 CD-ROM, 3 training booklets, 1991 (Box 163)